http://www.haztek-software.com/privacy.php

HazteK Software
The home of StorURL, TrueIP, SMTP Mail Sender and many other freeware tools
HomeDesktop ApplicationsOnline ApplicationsAboutContactBlogRSS
Toggle Dark Mode
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: July 10, 2019
Joey Hazlett/HazteK Software ("I", "us", "we", or "our") operates http(s)://www.haztek-software.com, http(s)://www.j3rk.us
(the "Site") and all sub-domains within. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive
from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance
with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally
Identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and email address ("Personal Information"). This information will only be requested in
the instance that you attempt to contact us. While we hope that you will provide valid information so that we may respond, we understand that your privacy is
very important.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data").
This Log Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and
date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, the number of times an application is downloaded and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.
Communications
We will use your Personal Information to contact you only if you request to be contacted. I have no intention of using this information for anything other
than responding to user questions or support requests.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored
on your computer's hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
We use Google to serve relevant advertisements to users of the site. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on user's prior
visits to the Site. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this Site and/or other sites
on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's
Ads Settings site. This Site has opted to disallow third party advertisers from displaying
advertisements to users.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage,
is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Interactions with the Site are encrypted using the
latest in free SSL certificates.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of (July 10, 2019) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions
in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time, and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the
Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgement of the modifications and your consent to abide
and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent
notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Licenses, Attributions, etc.
The Android robot is reproduced or modified from work created and shared by Google and used according to terms described in the Creative Commons 3.0 Attribution License.
Copyright © 2020 HazteK Software. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy • Become a Patron
